kean.edu 2016-10-22

# Privacy Policy | Kean University World Class Education

#### September 2015

Thank you for visiting the Kean University website and reviewing our Privacy Notice. This statement addresses collection, use and security of and access to information that may be obtained through the use of the Kean University web site. This notice covers the following topics:

  * Information Collected and How it is Used
  * Personal Information and Choice
  * Public Access to Information
  * Cookies
  * Security
  * Disclaimer
  * Contact Information

## Information Collected and Stored Automatically

The Internet domain (for example, “xcompany.com” if you use a private Internet access account, or “yourschool.edu” if you connect from a university’s domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our web site;

The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;

The date and time you access our site;

The pages you visit; and

If you linked to the New Jersey web site from another web site, the address of that web site.

We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors - to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.

If you choose to provide us with personal information via email or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through our web site, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. We do not create individual profiles with the information you provide or to give it to any private organizations. 

You may choose whether to provide personal information on-line.

Personal information is information about a natural person that is readily identifiable to that specific individual. Personal information includes such things as an individual’s name, address, and phone number. A domain name or Internet protocol address is not considered personal information.

We collect no personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us by sending us email, complete a request for information form or application, participate in a survey or complete another type of online form. You may choose not to contact us by email, participate in a survey, or provide any personal information using an online form. Your choice to not participate in these activities will not impair your ability to browse the Kean University web site and read or download any information provided on the site.

Email is not a secure medium. Personal information sent via the Internet can be intercepted. You may, therefore, wish to reconsider the advisability of sending messages that contain sensitive, personal information to this Intranet address.

NJOIT does not plan on divulging information collected or information disclosed voluntarily, but may be required to do so pursuant to a request under state right to know laws such as the New Jersey Open Public Records Act, any common law right to know laws, other State or Federal laws or pursuant to court order.

If you believe that your personal information is being used for a purpose other than what was intended when submitted, you may contact the [position] as shown in the Contact Information Section of this statement.

In the State of New Jersey, laws exist to ensure that public entities such as Kean University are open and that the public has a right to access appropriate records and information possessed by state governmental entities. At the same time, there are exceptions to the public’s right to access public records that serve various needs including the privacy of individuals. Exceptions are provided by both state and federal laws.

All the information collected at this site becomes public records that may be subject to inspection and copying by members of the public, unless an exemption in law exists.

Kean University uses cookies to customize and enhance your browsing experience. Cookies are simple text files stored on your computer by Internet web sites to help identify users and enhance customer service. Cookies created by using the Kean website may contain personally identifying information such as user contact information consisting of name, address, phone number or e-mail address. The cookie feature is used only to store a randomly generated identifying tag on your computer and does not compromise your privacy or security.

Kean University, as developer and manager of this website, has taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of its data and prevent unauthorized access to information maintained. These measures are designed and intended to prevent corruption of data, block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information, and to provide reasonable protection of private information in our possession.

The Kean University website and materials may contain hypertext or links to other Internet computer sites which are not owned, operated, controlled or reviewed by Kean University.. These links are provided solely as a courtesy and convenience to you, the visitor. When you link to one of these sites, you are no longer on the Kean University website and this Privacy Notice will not apply. When you link to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site.

Kean University, its agencies, officers, or employees exercise no control over the organizations, views, accuracy, copyright or trademark compliance or the legality of the material contained on those servers and do not sponsor, endorse, or approve the information, content, products, materials, opinions or services contained on such external sites. The visitor proceeds to these external sites at their own risk. Kean University specifically disclaims any and all liability from damages which may result from the accessing of a third party site which is linked to the Kean University website, or from reliance upon any such information.

You may contact Kean University via the contact below to review your personal information, or request correction of your personal information:

Office of University Relations  
Kean University  
1000 Morris Ave.  
Union, New Jersey 07083
